# **Daniel Burer**

hire@dburer.com

## Summary

Experienced and active software developer with a demonstrated history of performance in the Information Technology industry. Skilled in software engineering, full-stack web development, and digital design. Currently pursuing a Master of Science in Computer Science at Georgia Tech with a specialization in Machine Learning.

### Education

### **Georgia Institute of Technology**

Master of Science in Computer Science, Major GPA 4.0

Atlanta, GA May 2021

May 2018

Statesboro, GA

### **Georgia Southern University**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Major GPA 4.0

• Software Engineering Certificate

Game Programming Certificate

## **Professional Experience**

#### **Morris Technology**

Senior Solutions Developer

Statesboro, GA

February 2018 - Present

- Full-stack development of web-based Content Management System applications using JavaScript, React, Python, and the Django web framework
- Create, prototype, and implement responsive web design UI/UX for new features and the revision of outdated components
- Configure AWS architecture, containerization & autoscaling (Docker, Kubernetes), and integration with emergent serverless technologies (Lambda, API Gateway)
- Design and implement automated CI pipelines for building, testing, and deploying code to production systems (GitLab CI)
- Assist in coaching of junior developers, administrate team communication tools, and continuously streamline development environment
- Review, critique, and approve codebase modifications by team members before promotion of changes from development to production environments

# Junior Solutions Developer

April 2016 - February 2018

- Full stack development of web-based Content Management System applications
- Implementation and production of responsive web design frameworks built with HTML and SCSS
- Cross-platform mobile app development using Ionic and AngularJS frameworks
- Collaboratively developed using Git version control and regularly wrote unit/integration tests to a high coverage standard
- Provided direct customer support to perform regular codebase maintenance and implement new features

#### **Gulfstream Aerospace Corporation**

Pooler, GA

SAP Basis Intern

January 2017 - August 2017

- Performed multiple simultaneous 2017 Enhancement Pack upgrades on production SAP systems, including both ABAP and Java stacks
- Participated in regular daily sustainment and administrative activities including SAP note implementation, component patching, and SLES Linux kernel upgrades
- Assisted in the general workflow of Basis user problems and requests, accepting or dispatching to other Basis team members where appropriate

## **Core Qualifications**

- Proficiency in a broad set of software development skills, principles, languages, and platforms, both web-based and native
- Advanced knowledge of cloud architecture, containerization, and deployment
- Extensive experience in professional communication and performing with teams of varying sizes
- Continuous participation in Agile development, prototyping, and mentorship of intern-level team members

#### **Relevant Skills**

- Extensive and comprehensive full-stack web application development track record using JavaScript, CSS, Python, and associated frameworks/preprocessors including React, Angular, SASS, Node.js, and Django
- Proficient in general-purpose software development with high-level object-oriented languages (Java, Python, and C#)
- Well-versed in general cloud-computing architecture design and development (pursuing AWS certification), infrastructure-as-code (Terraform), and serverless computing
- Familiar and capable with major relational database technologies including PostgreSQL and MySQL
- Experienced in rapidly-evolving development team environments, project coordination and distribution, and unit/integration testing

#### **Honors**

#### **Georgia Southern President's List:**

- Fall 2014, 2017
- Spring 2015, 2016, 2017, 2018

#### **Scholarships**

- Zell Miller & HOPE Scholarship
- Georgia Southern President's Scholarship

#### Georgia Southern Dean's List

• Fall 2015, 2016

#### **Awards**

- Outstanding Scholar Graduating Senior
- Freshman Chemistry Award